const jsQuestions = [
    {
        question: "1: What does JS stand for?",
        choices: [
            "JavaSyntax",
            "JavaScript",
            "JustScript",
            "JScript"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "2: Which company developed JavaScript?",
        choices: [
            "Netscape",
            "Microsoft",
            "Sun Microsystems",
            "Oracle"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "3: Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;js&gt;",
            "&lt;scripting&gt;",
            "&lt;javascript&gt;",
            "&lt;script&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "4: What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'xxx.js'?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;script name='xxx.js'&gt;",
            "&lt;script src='xxx.js'&gt;",
            "&lt;script href='xxx.js'&gt;",
            "&lt;script link='xxx.js'&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "5: How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?",
        choices: [
            "alertBox('Hello World');",
            "msg('Hello World');",
            "msgBox('Hello World');",
            "alert('Hello World');"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "6: How do you create a function in JavaScript?",
        choices: [
            "function myFunction()",
            "function:myFunction()",
            "function = myFunction()",
            "function => myFunction()"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "7: How do you call a function named 'myFunction'?",
        choices: [
            "call myFunction()",
            "call function myFunction()",
            "myFunction()",
            "call myFunction"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "8: How to write an IF statement in JavaScript?",
        choices: [
            "if i = 5 then",
            "if i == 5 then",
            "if (i == 5)",
            "if i = 5"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "9: How to write an IF statement for executing some code if 'i' is NOT equal to 5?",
        choices: [
            "if (i != 5)",
            "if i &lt;&gt; 5",
            "if (i &gt; 5)",
            "if i &gt; 5"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "10: How does a WHILE loop start?",
        choices: [
            "while (i &lt;= 10)",
            "while (i &lt;= 10; i++)",
            "while i &lt;= 10",
            "while (i &lt; 10)"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "11: How does a FOR loop start?",
        choices: [
            "for i = 1 to 5",
            "for (i &lt;= 5; i++)",
            "for (i = 0; i &lt;= 5)",
            "for (i = 0; i &lt;= 5; i++)"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "12: How can you add a comment in JavaScript?",
        choices: [
            "'This is a comment",
            "//This is a comment",
            "&lt;!--This is a comment--&gt;",
            "!--This is a comment--"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "13: What is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?",
        choices: [
            "var colors = (1:'red', 2:'green', 3:'blue')",
            "var colors = 'red', 'green', 'blue'",
            "var colors = ['red', 'green', 'blue']",
            "var colors = 1 = ('red'), 2 = ('green'), 3 = ('blue')"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "14: How do you round the number 7.25 to the nearest integer?",
        choices: [
            "Math.round(7.25)",
            "Math.rnd(7.25)",
            "Math.roundNum(7.25)",
            "round(7.25)"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "15: How do you find the number with the highest value of x and y?",
        choices: [
            "ceil(x, y)",
            "Math.ceil(x, y)",
            "Math.max(x, y)",
            "top(x, y)"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "16: What is the correct JavaScript syntax for opening a new window called 'w2'?",
        choices: [
            "w2 = window.new('http://www.example.com');",
            "w2 = window.open('http://www.example.com');",
            "w2 = window.openWindow('http://www.example.com');",
            "w2 = window.create('http://www.example.com');"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "17: JavaScript is the same as Java.",
        choices: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "18: Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?",
        choices: [
            "onchange",
            "onmouseclick",
            "onmouseover",
            "onclick"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "19: How do you declare a JavaScript variable?",
        choices: [
            "var carName;",
            "v carName;",
            "variable carName;",
            "carName = var;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "20: Which operator is used to assign a value to a variable?",
        choices: [
            "*",
            "x",
            "=",
            "-"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    }
];
